Guide to the General Frederick Steele Papers, 1845-1965 (inclusive), 1862-1868 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series IA. Correspondence and papers of General Frederick Steele, 1845-1890.
  - Correspondence 1865, April 15-19. (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - 32. 1865, Apr. 17.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 70. Printed. Extension of military lines of U.S.
    - 33. 1865, Apr. 18.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. LS. Sends record of general court martial.
    - 34. 1865, Apr. 18.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 28. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. G. L. Andrews given power to administer oath of amnesty.
    - 35. 1865, Apr. 18.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 37, extract 2. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. New Cavalry Brigade, Knipe.
    - 36. 1865, Apr. 18.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 37, extract 5. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Leave for Compton.
    - 37. 1865, Apr. 18.H. Bertram to C. C. Andrews. Tel. Request to go to Mobile.
    - 38. 1865, Apr. 18.H. Bertram to J. F. Lacey. Tel. Picket at Bayou Minnette.
    - 39. 1865, Apr. 18.H. Bertram to J. F. Lacey. Tel. Quarter master stores and sick.
    - 40. 1865, Apr. 18.C. T. Christensen to FS. Tel. Company of 2nd New Jersey Cavalry.
    - 41. 1865, Apr. 18.C. T. Christensen to FS. Tel. No cavalry for Bertram.
    - 42. 1865, Apr. 18.C. T. Christensen to FS. Tel. Company to look after guerrillas.
    - 43. 1865, Apr. 18.C. T. Christensen to FS. Tel. Requests FS to come to Mobile to see [Canby].
    - 44. 1865, Apr. 18.C. T. Christensen to FS. Tel. Re: 1st Louisiana and 2nd New Jersey Cavalry.
    - 45. 1865, Apr. 18.Chas. S. McEntee to [J. F.] Lacey. ADS. Assignment of steamers for transport of Hawkins' command.
    - 46. 1865, Apr. 18.Wm. Marland to J. F. Lacey. Tel. Re: H. R. Seele.
    - 47. 1865, Apr. 19.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 27. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Citizens of Mobile, etc.
    - 48. 1865, Apr. 19.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 28. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Freedmen and former slaves.
    - 49. 1865, Apr. 19.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 38, extract 3. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Artillery to Hawkins.
    - 50. 1865, Apr. 19.G. [T. I Beauregard [sic] to H. Cobbs. Copy. Truce.
    - 51. 1865, Apr. 19.C. T. Christensen to FS. Tel. Negroes.
    - 52. 1865, Apr. 19.1st Michigan Light Artillery - Battery G. Morning Report, s. George L. Stillman.
    - 53. 1865, Apr. 19.Alfred Fredberg to J. F. Lacey. ANS. Sends G.F.O.s, etc.
    - 54. 1865, Apr. 19.Joseph Lyman to no. F. Lacey. Tel. Embarking.
    - 55. 1865, Apr. 19.[Mobile Ordnance Dept.]. S.O. No. 18, extract 2, s. Wm. Hunt. 18th N.Y. Battery report to FS.
    - 56. 1865, Apr. 19.L. W. Swan to Provost Marshall. NS. Refugees.
    - 57. 1865, Apr. 19.Jas. Totten to FS. Tel. Artillery.
    - 58. 1865, Apr. 19.Jas. Totten to FS. Tel. Artillery horses.
    - 59. 1865, Apr. 19.U.S. Forces Operating from Pensacola Bay (March). Return for March.
    - 60. 1865, Apr. 19.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 71. Printed. Military Division of the James.
  - Correspondence 1865, April 20-24. (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - 1. 1865, Apr. 20.Archer Anderson to Howell Cobb. Copy. Armistice.
    - 2. 1865, Apr. 20.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 29. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Announces death of President and Secretary of State.
    - 3. 1865, Apr. 20.C. T. Christensen to FS. [ALS?]. Water transportation.
    - 4. 1865, Apr. 20.18th New York Independent Battery. Consolidate Morning report, s. A. G. Mack.
    - 5. 1865, Apr. 20.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Tri-Monthly Report, s. John P. Hawkins and Sam'l. B. Ferguson.
    - 6. 1865, Apr. 20.1st Michigan Light Artillery-Battery G. Tri-Monthly Report, s. George L. Stillman.
    - 7. 1865, Apr. 20.1st Michigan Light Artillery - Battery G. Tri-Monthly Report, s. George L. Stillman. ANS of Jos. Lyman.
    - 8. 1865, Apr. 20.John F. Lacey to C. C. Andrews. ANS. Ammunition?
    - 9-10. 1865, Apr. 20.C. S. McEntee to FS. 2 tels. Embarking.
    - 11. 1865, Apr. 20.Lawrence Rhoades to John F. Lacey. ANS. Guard on steamers.
    - 12. 1865, Apr. [20].C. G. Sawtelle to [C. S.] McEntee. Tel. Must transport Mack's Battery.
    - 13. 1865, Apr. 20.2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. Tri-Monthly Report, s. C. C. Andrews and George Monroe.
    - 14. 1865, Apr. 20.U.S. Forces East of Mobile Bay. Tri-Monthly Report.
    - 15. 1865, Apr. 20.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 72. Printed. General Officers and Guard of Honor on funeral train.
    - 16. 1865, Apr. 20.Jules C. Webber to J. F. Lacey. ANS. Rank and regiment.
    - 17. 1865, Apr. 21.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 30. Printed. Rebel Government property, private property, commerce, lines of occupation, trade permits.
    - 18. 1865, Apr. 21.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 40, extract 1. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. FS to disembark a brigade.
    - 19. 1865, Apr. 21.D. B. Harmony to [J. F.] Lacey. ANS. code of signals wanted.
    - 20. 1865, Apr. [21?].John P. Hawkins to John F. Lacey. NS. 7th Massachusetts Battery.
    - 21. 1865, Apr. 21.J. E. Johnston to Gen'l. Wilson. Copy s. G. M. H[azen?]. Sherman communicates universal suspension of hostilities.
    - 22. 1865, Apr. 21.U.S. Forces East of Mobile Bay. Tri-Monthly Field Return, s. FS.
    - 23. 1865, Apr. 21.War Department - A.G.O. General Court Martia Orders [G.C.M.O.] No. 199. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Pardon of James P. Harry.
    - 24. 1865, Apr. 22.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 31. Printed. Furloughs.
    - 25. 1865, Apr. 22.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 32. Printed. Results of Mobile-Blakely campaign, thanks.
    - 26. 1865, Apr. 22.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 41, extract 1. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Leave for Gower.
    - 27. 1865, Apr. 24.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 43, extract 3. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Dishonorable discharge of Cross.
    - 28. 1865, Apr. 24.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 73. Printed. Attorney General's opinion re: rebel officers, etc.
    - 29. 1865, Apr. 24.J. B. Wheeler to [FS]. ALS. Personal, mare and colt, Little Rock.
  - Correspondence 1865, April 25-30. (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - 1. 1865, Apr. 25.Post of Montgomery. G.O. No. 1. Geddes in command.
    - 2. 1865, Apr. 25.Post of Montgomery. G.O. No. 2. Inhabitants to resume peaceful activities, give up firearms, obey curfew, etc.
    - 3. 1865, Apr. 25.10th Army Corps. S.O. No. 38, extract 2. 3rd Brigade, 3rd Division to garrison and guard Montgomery.
    - 4. 1865, Apr. 26.G. [H.] Thomas to Jas. [H.] Wilson. Copy. Armistice disapproved by U.S., terms of surrender.
    - 5. 1865, Apr. 26.U.S. Forces Expedition Steamer Tarascon. S.O. No. 19, extract 2, s. R. Kennicott, Herman Walford, Gallio Fairman. Docket: s. John F. Lacey. Board of Appraisal.
    - 6. 1865, Apr. 26.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 74. Printed. Military lines of U.S.
    - 7. 1865, Apr. 26.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 75. Printed. Exchange POWs.
    - 8. 1865, Apr. 26.Board of Examiners of Commissaries of Subsistence, 6th District, New Orleans. S.O. No. 1, copy by Lawrence Rhoades. A. R. Smith to report.
    - 9. 1865, Apr. 27.W. F. Bullock, Jr. to Y. L. Royston. Tel. Sherman-Johnston armistice, instructions.
    - 10. 1865, Apr. 27.Division of Mississippi, in the field, Raleig N.C. S.F.O. No. 65, s. S. L. Woodward. Terminates war with Johnston, receiving arms.
    - 11. 1865, Apr. 27.N. W. Storer to John F. Lacey. LS.
    - 12. 1865, Apr. 27.G. H. Thomas to J. H. Wilson. Copy by S. L. Woodward. Confederate specie being moved, to disregard Sherman, extracts from Stanton letter.
    - 13. 1865, Apr. 27.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 76. Printed. Instructions re: Veteran Reserve Corps.
    - 14. 1865, Apr. 28.C. C. Jones to John F. Lacey. LS. Need for supplied. Docket: NSs of W. T. Spicely and C. C. Andrews.
    - 15. 1865, Apr. 28.Wm. A. Pile to J. F. Lacey. LS. Requests leave of absence. Docket: ANS of John P. Hawkins.
    - 16. 1865, Apr. 28.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 77. Printed. For reducing Expenses of the Military Establishment.
    - 17. 1865, Apr. 29.1st Division, U. S. Colored Troops. Tri-Monthly Return, s. John P. Hawkins.
    - 18. 1865, Apr. 29.Lewis K. Harris to Fred. T. Lewis. ANS. Request to send man for books and desks. Docket: NSs of W. T. Spicely and C. C. Andrews.
    - 19. 1865, Apr. 29.Chas. S. McEntee to J. F. Lacey. ANS. Send man to take charge of cotton at Mobile.
    - 20. 1865, Apr. 29.J. A. Marshall to [FS?]. ALS. Asks about terms of surrender. Docket: ANS 5/6 of Joseph [Lyman?].
    - 21. 1865, Apr. 29.Y. L. Royston to Gen. Wilson or Commanding Officer around Selma. Copy. Protests a Federal raid.
    - 22. 1865, Apr. 29.18th Independent Battery, Light Artillery, New York State Volunteers. Return s. A. G. Mack.
    - 23. 1865, Apr. 29.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Tri-Monthly Field Return, s. John P. Hawkins, dated 5/3.
    - 24. 1865, Apr. 29.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Tri-Monthly Report, s. Sam'l. B. Ferguson and John P. Hawkins, dated 5/5.
    - 25. 1865, Apr. 29.J. E. Johnston to McLaws or Fry. Copy tel., s. S. L. Woodward. G.O. No. 18 of Army of Tennessee re: surrender and disbanding.
    - 26. 1865, Apr. 29.P. Jos. Osterhaus to FS. LS. Sherman-Hohnston armistice disapproved by President.
    - 27. 1865, Apr. 30.2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. Return, s. George Monroe and C. C. Andrews.
    - 28. 1865, Apr. 30.2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. Tri Monthly Report, s. George Monroe and C. C. Andrews.
    - 29. 1865, Apr. 30.U.S. Expedition Forces. Tri Monthly Report, s. John F. Lacey and FS.
    - 30. [1865, Apr.]E. P. Adams. Signal message. 7 a.m. Position of steamers.
    - 31. [1865, Apr.].[E. R. S.] Canby to FS. Tel. What is the matter on your left.
    - 32. [1865, Apr.].C. M. Denicke to E. R. S. Canby. Signal message. Reports Forts Huger and Tracy evacuated.
    - 33. [1865, Apr.].S. M. Eaton. DS. Rebel troops at Spanish Fort and Blakely.
    - 34. [1865, Apr.].R. P. Strong. Signal message. 10 a.m. and 10:30 a.m. Steamers.
  - Maps [1865, April].Spanish Fort, Blakely, and Mobile. (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - 1. Mobile-Blakely. North to New Wakefield and Choctaw Bluff. Hand executed.
    - 2. Plan Shewing the Defences of Blakely. Hand executed.
    - 3. Blakely and Mobile River. Many notations, torpedoes in Mobile Riber, etc. Hand executed.
    - 4. In Front of Spanish Fort. North to Blakely and East to Hollyoke's. Hand executed.
    - 5. In Front of Blakely. North to Choctaw Bluff and East to Perdido Station. Hand executed.
  - Correspondence 1865, May 1-6. (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - 1. 1865, May 1.C. C. Andrews to FS. ALS. Selma, Ala., J. Davis going West.
    - 2. 1865, May 1.13th New York Independent Battery Volunteers. Ds. Consolidated Morning Report, s. A.G. Mack.
    - 3. 1865, May 11.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. G.O. No. 20. DS of Sam'l. B. Ferguson. Orders women out of camps.
    - 4. 1865, May 1.Lawrence Rhoades to J. F. Lacey. ANS.
    - 5. 1865, May 1.16th Army Corps. S.O. No. 44, extract 1. DS of J. Hough. Surplus horses to citizens.
    - 6-7. 1865, May 1.U.S. Expeditionary Forces. 2 Consolidated Tri-Monthly Field Returns. One s. FS, other unsigned.
    - 8. 1865, May 1.U.S. Forces Northern Alabama. G.O. No. 1. Printed. FS takes command.
    - 9. 1865, May 1.U.S. Forces Northern Alabama. G.O. No. 2. Printed. FS's staff.
    - 10. 1865, May 1.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 78. Printed. Warren replaces Dana as commander of Dept. of Mississippi.
    - 11. 1865, May 1.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 79. Printed. Reducing number of officers.
    - 12. 1865, May 1.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 80. Printed. Grant's aide.
    - 13. 1865, May 2.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 33. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Rebel officers to report.
    - 14. 1865, May 2.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 34. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Assistant chief quarter master.
    - 15. 1865, May 2.13th Army Corps. G.O. No. 22 /Commissary and Quarter Master, supplies for pioneer companies.
    - 16. 1865, May 2.Wm. Thompson to FS. ALS. Congratulations, Mobile campaign, asks recommend.
    - 17. 1865, May 2.J. H. Wilson to B. H. Grierson. Copy s. S. L. Woodward. Collapse of Confederacy, look for Davis.
    - 18. 1865, May 3.C. C. Andrews to FS. ANS.
    - 19. 1865, May 3.C. C. Andrews to FS. ALS. Colored men want to join service.
    - 20. 1865, May 3.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 35. Printed. Police regulations.
    - 21. 1865, May 3.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 52. Printed. Resignation.
    - 22-23. 1865, May 3.Chas. [S.] McEntee to J. Lyman. 2 ANSs. Notes, different content.
    - 24. 1865, May 3.P.J. Osterhaus and E. R. S. Canby and R. Taylor to FS. Tel. Desist from further Hostilities.
    - 25. 1865, May 3.Jas. Totten to FS. DS Springfield Rifle Muskets.
    - 26. 1865, May 3.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 81. Printed. Discharge all arms to prevent accident.
    - 27. 1865, May 4.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 53. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Leave of absence.
    - 28. 1865, May 4. ___. ___.Lee (Col. 2nd New York Cavalry) to [J. F.] Lacey. ANS.
    - 29. 1865, May 4.FS to Gov. T. H. Watts. Copy. Safe conduct waiting for word of end of war.
    - 30. 1865, May 4.U.S. Forces Northern Alabama. G.O. No. 3 Printed.
    - 31. 1865, May 5.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. ANS.
    - 32-33. 1865, May 5.(Mrs.) E. ___. Tipton to C. C. Andrews. ANS and certificate enclosed in #31. FS's troops killed livestock on her plantation. Certificate endorsed by Andrews.
    - 34. 1865, May 5.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 36. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Surrender of R. Taylor.
    - 35. 1865, May 5.E. S. [Leady?] to [FS]. ALS. Robbery and hanging by U.S. Troops.
    - 36. 1865, May 5.Lawrence Rhoades to John F. Lacey. ANS.
    - 37. 1865, May 6.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. ALS. Shortage of rations.
    - 38. 1865, May 6.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 37. Printed.
    - 39. 1865, May 6.Army Navy Journal. Account of fall of Mobile, etc.
    - 40. 1865, May 6.Charles Black to Lt. [J.] Lyman. ANS. Collect provisions, escort for train.
    - 41. 1865, May 6.16th Army Corps. S.O. No. 49, extract 2, s. J. Hough. Commissary at Montgomery.
    - 42. 1865, May 6.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 82. Printed. Reducing officers.
    - 43. 1865, May 6.John M. Wilson to C. T. Christensen. ANS. List of AWOLs.
  - Correspondence 1865, May 7-13. (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - 1. 1865, May 7.Lawrence Rhoades to John F. Lacey. ALS. Commissaries.
    - 2. 1865, May 8.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 57, extract 1. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Detained enlisted men.
    - 3. 1865, May 8.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 57, extract 2. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Leave of absence.
    - 4. 1865, May 8.T. J. Lucas to John F. Lacey. LS. Asks return of Company H, 1st Louisiana Cavalry. Docket: 5/8 ANS of B. H. Grierson.
    - 5. 1865, May 8.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 83. Printed. Reduce Volunteer Cavalry forces.
    - 6. 1865, May 8.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 84. Printed. Bounties.
    - 7. 1865, May 8.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 85. Printed. Prisoners of war.
    - 8. 1865, May 9.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 58, extract 1. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Discontinue recruiting offices.
    - 9. 1865, May 9.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 58, extract 2. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Leave of absence.
    - 10. 1865, May 9.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No1 86. Printed. Lists to be made of Volunteer officers.
    - 11. 1865, May 9.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 87. Printed. Engineers property and labor on Field-works.
    - 12. 1865, May 10.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 38. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Captured property.
    - 13. 1865, May 10.Army and Division of West Mississippi. G.F.O. No. 39. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Confederate cotton.
    - 14. 1865, May 10.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Tri-Monthly Report, s. John P. Hawkins and Sam'l. B. Ferguson.
    - 15. 1865, May 10.2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. Tri-Monthly Report, s. C. C. Andrews and Jno. B. Mitchell.
    - 16. 1865, May 10.U.S. Forces Northern Alabama. Tri-Monthly Report, unsigned.
    - 17. 1865, May 10.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 88. Printed. Price of furlough rations.
    - 18. 1865, May 10.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 89. Printed. Exchange prisoners.
    - 19. 1865, May 11.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 60, extract 2. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Transfer troops.
    - 20. 1865, May 11.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 60, extract 3. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. 1st Missouri Light Artillery.
    - 21-22. 1865, May 11.U.S. Forces Northern Alabama. Consolidated Tri-Monthly Field Return. (2)
    - 23. 1865, May 11.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 90. Printed. Punishment of guerrillas.
    - 24. 1865, May 11.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 222, extract 27. Printed. Dismissal.
    - 25. 1865, May 12.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 91. Printed. Order organization of Bureau of Refugees, Freedmen and Abandoned Lands.
    - 26. 1865, May 12.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 92. Printed. Public horses purchased by officers.
    - 27. 1865, May 13.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 130, extract 3. Printed, s. C. H. Dyer. Re: E. H. Newton.
    - 28. 1865, May 13.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 93. Printed. Tents, etc. used in contagious diseases to be burned.
    - 29. 1865, May 13.War Department - A.G.O. G.C.M.O. No. 234. Printed. Release of George Copeland.
  - Correspondence 1865, May 15-31. (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - 1. 1865, May 15.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 1 Reports of troops mustered out.
    - 2. 1865, May 15.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 94. Printed. Discharge rules.
    - 3. 1865, May 15.War Department - Bureau of Refugees, Freedmen, and Abandoned Lands. Printed circular No. 1. Staff of O. O. Howard.
    - 4. 1865, May 16.War Department - A.G.O. Printed circular No. 1 Places for pay to be forwarded.
    - 5. 1865, May 17.Army and Division of West Mississippi. S.F.O. No. 65, extract 4. Printed, s. Alfred Fredberg. Surgeon transferred from FS.
    - 6. 1865, May 17.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 95. Printed. Military Division of West Mississippi abolished, Sheridan and Banks relieved of command.
    - 7. 1865, May 18.War Department - A.G.O. G.C.M.O. No. 238. Printed, s. F. W. Emery.
    - 8. 1865, May 18.War Department - A.G.O. G.C.M.O. No. 241. Printed.
    - 9. 1865, May 18.War Department - A.G.O. G.C.M.O. No. 246. Printed.
    - 10. 1865, May 18.[L. L. Zulavsky?] to Samuel B. Ferguson. LS. Re: insulting safeguard. Docket: ANS of John P. Hawkins.
    - 11. 1865, May 19.1st Division, U.S. Colored Troops. Return. DS of John B. Hawkins and Sam'l. B. Ferguson.
    - 12. 1865, May 19.Arden R. Smith to John F. Lacey. ALS.
    - 13. 1865, May 19.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 96. Printed.
    - 14. 1865, May 19.War Department - Bureau of Refugees, etc. Printed Circular No. 2, s. R. F. Halsted. Howard takes command.
    - 15. 1865, May 20.U.S. Forces [Northern Alabama]. Return.
    - 16. 1865, May 21.U. S. Grant to FS. ALS. Sheridan to take command West of the Mississippi and South of the Arkansas, to reoccupy Texas, FS to set up strong foothold on Rio Grande.
    - 17. 1865, May 21.John P. Hawkins to FS. ANS on a docket.
    - 18a. 1865, May 22.B. F. Wade to FS. LS. For Senate Committee on Conduct of the War, includes questions.
    - 18b. 1865, May 22.War Department - Bureau of Refugees, etc. Printed Circular No. 3, s. R. F. Halsted. Abandoned lands.
    - 19. 1865, May 24.A. Fredberg to E. R. S. Canby. Tel. with deciphered message 5/18 U. S. Grant to E. R. S. Canby. Galveston expedition cancelled, FS to go to Rio Grande.
    - 20. 1865, May 25.FS to Jno. F. Lacey. Tel. Troops to concentrate at Mobile Bay.
    - 21. 1865, May 26.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 142, extract 5, s. C. H. Dyer. Officers to report to FS.
    - 22. 1865, May 26.FS to J. F. Lacey. Tel. Rations.
    - 23. 1865, May 26.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 97. Printed Promotions, appointments, resignations, etc.
    - 24. 1865, May 27.Geo. A. Mitchell to [FS]. ALS. Personal and finance.
    - 25. 1865, May 27.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 98. Printed. Sentences by Military Tribunals.
    - 26. 1865, May 27.War Department - A.G.O. G.C.M.O. No. 252. Printed.
    - 27. 1865, May 28.Devicione Mejia - Parque de Artilleria. DS of [J]. Maria Cabella and Pedro Navarrete. In Spanish.
    - 28. 1865, May 28.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 144, extract. 12. Printed, s. C. H. Dyer. Engineer C. J. Allen.
    - 29. 1865, May 28.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 99. Printed. Recruiting.
    - 30. 1865, Mayh 28.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 100. Printed. Commutation of rations.
    - 31. 1865, May 29.Army and Division of West Mississippi. to FS. Printed circular letter s. Alfred Fredberg. Headquarters move.
    - 32. 1865, May 29.E. R. S. Canby to FS. Tel. FS to sail for Rio Grande.
    - 33. 1865, May 29.War Department - Bureau of Refugees, etc. Printed Circular No. 4, s. R. F. Halsted.
    - 34. 1865, May 29.War Department - Bureau of Refugees, etc. Printed Circular No. 5. Rules and Regulations for Assistant Commissioners.
    - 35. 1865, May 30.13th Army Corps. S. O. No. 63, extract 1, s. F. W. Emery. 21st New York Battery.
    - 36. 1865, May 30.13th Army Corps. S.O. No. 63, extract 2., s. F. W. Emery. Battery F, 1st Missouri Artille
    - 37. 1865, May 30.13th Army Corps. S.O. No. 63, extract 3, s. F. W. Emery. 3rd Division assigned to FS.
    - 38. 1865, May 30.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 101. Printed Retention of arms.
    - 39. 1865, May 31.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 64. Copy. Muster out white volunteers.
    - 40. 1865, May 31.Jas. Totten to FS. LS. Ordnance estimates.
    - 41. 1865, May 31.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 102. Printed Cooperation with Bureau of Refugees.
    - 42. 1865, May 31.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 103. Printed Exchanged prisoners.
    - 43. 1865, May 31.War Department - A.G.O. G.C.M.O. No. 259. Printed, s. F. W. Emery.
  - Correspondence 1865, June 1-10. (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - 1. 1865, Jun. 1.E. R. S. Canby to FS. LS. FS ordered to Rio Grande for occupation, international relations with Mexico, construct railroad from Brazos to Rio Grande.
    - 2. 1865, Jun. 1.R. H. McKitrick, C. H. Cunningham and L. A. [Marlow]. DS. Proceedings of a Board of Survey. Docket: NS of Wm. E. Stevens.
    - 3. 1865, Jun. 1.War Department - A.G.O. Printed Circular No. 20 s. F. W. Emery. Commissaries and Assistant Commissaries of Musters.
    - 4. 1865, Jun. 2.P. H. Sheridan to FS. LS. Weitzel's instructions, relate information on rebels crossing into Mexico and Mexico.
    - 5. 1865, Jun. 2.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 104. Printed. Furnished Prisoners transport when released on taking oath.
    - 6. 1865, Jun. 2.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 105. Printed. Reduction of Volunteer Artillery.
    - 7. 1865, Jun. 2.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 106. Printed. Relieve General and Staff officers.
    - 8. 1865, Jun. 2.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 107. Printed. Removal of restrictions on trade.
    - 9. 1865, Jun. 2.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 108. Printed. Grant's thanks to soldiers of Armies of U.S.
    - 10. 1865, Jun. 3.C. T. Christensen to FS. ALS. Personal, retiring from service, regards from Canbys.
    - 11. 1865, Jun. 3.Jos. R. Smith to [FS]. ALS. Personal, Arkansas news, badge design for 7th Army Corps.